<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Gay City</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">Android Studio</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">android.studio@android.com</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <string name="menu_home">Home</string>
    <string name="menu_gallery">Gallery</string>
    <string name="menu_slideshow">Slideshow</string>
    <string name="about_gay_city">About Gay City</string>
    <string name="our_vision">Our Vision</string>
    <string name="vision_description">Gay City is the definitive hub for LGBTQ individuals seeking affirming and responsive resources, wellness, and community.</string>
    <string name="our_mission">Our Mission</string>
    <string name="mission_description">Gay City: Seattle’s LGBTQ Center cultivates access and connections to promote self&#8211;determination, liberation and joy in our communities.</string>
    <string name="our_values">Our Values</string>
    <string name="advocacy">Advocacy</string>
    <string name="advocacy_description">Gay City: Seattle’s LGBTQ Center cultivates access and connections to promote self&#8211;determination, liberation and joy in our communities.</string>
    <string name="accessibility">Accessibility</string>
    <string name="accessibility_description">Gay City: Seattle’s LGBTQ Center cultivates access and connections to promote self&#8211;determination, liberation and joy in our communities.</string>
    <string name="intersectionality">Intersectionality</string>
    <string name="Intersectionality_description">We recognize that our community members are multifaceted, with overlapping and intersecting identities. We seek to honor our interdependent identities in all our services and programming. We also recognize that LGBTQ communities face multiple and intersecting forms of structural oppression. We are committed to honoring those truths in all that we do.</string>
    <string name="sex_and_body_positivity">Sex and Body Positivity</string>
    <string name="positivity_description">Gay City values all bodies and consensual sexuality. We defer judgment when people seek support or share their diverse stories and invest in people’s self&#8211;determination.</string>
    <string name="stewardship">Stewardship</string>
    <string name="strewardship_description">Gay City takes community seriously. We act in service of people’s daily needs, and towards our greater liberation, as they are not separate. We know the power of community and take great care in building it for today and generations to come.</string>
    <string name="transparency">Transparency</string>
    <string name="transparancy_description">Gay City sees transparency being key in creating equitable outcomes and getting people what they need to be successful. We have established policies, procedures, and practices with the intent to be clear and open with the communities we serve.</string>
    <string name="our_history">Our History</string>
    <string name="history_description">2020 marks Gay City’s 25th year of building resilience and joy in LGBTQ communities. <br />In 1995, a group of community activists launched Gay City with a bold vision of building a community stronger than HIV while centering queer voices. This mission evolved in the 2000s when the organization introduced its Wellness Center, Arts Programs, and established a physical space where all LGBTQ people could be themselves. <br />Today, Gay City remains the leading HIV/STI tester in King County, home to several LGBTQ&#8211;affirming services, and provides access to hundreds of resources. The organization is also an active force in queer youth engagement and provides LGBTQ&#8211;centered trainings that address the needs of the most marginalized people within our community.</string>
    <string name="register_now">Register now</string>
    <string name="learn_more">Learn more</string>
    <string name="popup_content_description">in image for the back of the popup</string>
    <string name="popup_x_content_description">an x image to exit the popup</string>
    <string name="phone">PHONE</string>
    <string name="website">WEBSITE</string>
    <string name="resources_availability">RESOURCES AVAILABILITY</string>
    <string name="services_availability">SERVICES AVAILABILITY</string>
    <string name="services_and_resources">SERVICES AND RESOURCES</string>
    <string name="values">VALUES</string>
    <string name="vision">VISION</string>
    <string name="mission">MISSION</string>
    <string name="email">EMAIL</string>
    <string name="communities">COMMUNITIES</string>
    <string name="basic_needs_supports">BASIC NEEDS SUPPORTS</string>
    <string name="access_needs">ACCESS NEEDS</string>
    <string name="trans_and_gender_non_conforming_affirming_services">TRANS AND GENDER NON&#8211;CONFORMING AFFIRMING SERVICES</string>
    <string name="bipoc_lgbtq_affirming_services">BIPOC LGBTQ+ AFFIRMING SERVICES</string>
    <string name="lgbtq_youth_affirming_services">LGBTQ+ YOUTH AFFIRMING SERVICES</string>
    <string name="lgbtq_adult_affirming_services">LGBTQ+ ADULT AFFIRMING SERVICES</string>
    <string name="wait_for_the_election_results">Wait for the Election Results</string>
    <string name="_08">08</string>
    <string name="create_a_backup_plan">Create a Backup Plan</string>
    <string name="track_ballot_now">Track Ballot Now</string>
    <string name="_10_ways_to_prepare_for_an_election">10 WAYS TO PREPARE FOR AN ELECTION</string>
    <string name="_10_ways_to_prepare_for_an_election_description">Here are ten ways to prepare for any upcoming election. The tips may differ depending on the city, county and state where you live, so we have included some national resources for those that live outside King County (Washington State). <br />If at any point you need help (accessibility concerns or otherwise), contact your local elections office for help: <br />• King County (WA): 206&#8211;296&#8211;vote <br />• United States: 1&#8211;866&#8211;OUR&#8211;VOTE or 888&#8211;VE&#8211;Y&#8211;VOTA. <br />Please share any election preparation tips you have to communications@gaycity.org.</string>
    <string name="_01">01</string>
    <string name="are_you_eligible_to_vote">Are you Eligible to Vote?</string>
    <string name="eligible_description">To register to vote in the state of Washington, you must be: <br />• A citizen of the United States <br />• A legal resident of Washington state for at least 30 days prior to election day <br />• At least 18 years old by election day <br />• Not disqualified from voting due to a court order <br />• Not under Department of Corrections supervision for a Washington felony conviction <br />Not 18 years old? <br />If you meet all of the requirements, except you’re 16 or 17, you can pre&#8211;register to vote. Your registration will be held by the elections office until you become eligible to vote.</string>
    <string name="check_registration">Check REgistration</string>
    <string name="_03">03</string>
    <string name="register_to_vote">Register to Vote</string>
    <string name="track_your_ballot">Track Your Ballot</string>
    <string name="_07">07</string>
    <string name="voter_elgibility">Voter Elgibility</string>
    <string name="_02">02</string>
    <string name="check_your_voter_registration">Check Your Voter Registration</string>
    <string name="voter_registration_description">Whether you registered last year or recently registered, make sure your registration was processed correctly – verify your name and address. <br />Sometimes people are purged from the rolls or simple computer glitches, so we encourage you to take a few minutes to check your registration.</string>
    <string name="register_to_vote_description">Unable to find your registration in the polls? Does your registration have your dead name, but your ID have your real name? Has your address changed? <br />These are just some of the reasons to register to vote. <br />Here are the things you need to register: <br />• Complete a voter registration card online, in person, or print and mail it to the elections office. <br />• King County (Washington State) | Provide a copy of an approved ID: <br />• Driver’s license <br />• State ID card <br />• Student ID card <br />• Tribal ID card <br />• Employer ID card <br />• Outside King County | Provide a copy of an approved ID: <br />• Learn more at voteriders.org.</string>
    <string name="complete_voter_registration">Complete voter registration</string>
    <string name="_04">04</string>
    <string name="request_an_early_vote_absentee_ballot">Request an Early Vote (Absentee) Ballot</string>
    <string name="absentee_ballot_description">Contact your local elections office to request a printed vote early ballot or to vote online. <br />Even in the few states where ballots are sent automatically, you should still ensure your ballot has been sent and when to expect it. Sometimes there are computer glitches or mailing issues that arise, and you don’t want that to keep you from voting. <br />In King County (Washington State) you can call (206) 296&#8211;VOTE. <br />Outside King County you can call 1&#8211;866&#8211;OUR&#8211;VOTE.</string>
    <string name="_05">05</string>
    <string name="do_your_research">Do Your Research</string>
    <string name="do_your_research_description">You’re halfway there to completing the your preparation for the election. But, this is one of the biggest steps of them all – know what you’re voting for. <br />Here are some ways to research the candidates and the referendums: <br />• Vote411 <br />• Ballotpedia <br />• Contact the candidates and their party to ask your questions <br />• Read articles from trusted media sources who cite their sources or have media that is moderately edited</string>
    <string name="_06">06</string>
    <string name="follow_all_ballot_instructions">Follow All Ballot Instructions</string>
    <string name="ballot_instructions_description">Instructions will accompany your Vote Early (Absentee) ballot. Follow instructions as noted, ensure you’re using the correct marking tool (e.g. pen or pencil). <br />Remember to sign your envelope as well. <br />If you have further questions about how to complete your ballot and return it to your elections office, please call the following offices: <br />• In King County (Washington State) you can call (206) 296&#8211;VOTE. <br />• Outside King County you can call 1&#8211;866&#8211;OUR&#8211;VOTE.</string>
    <string name="track_your_ballot_description">For early voting ballots, remember you can track your ballot from the elections office to your home and from your home to the office online. <br />If your ballot remains missing on Election Day, you may need to vote in person with a provisional ballot to ensure you only vote once. View the next step to learn more about voting in person.</string>
    <string name="backup_plan_description">If you made a mistake, your ballot is missing on Election Day, or you never received their ballot, you may need to visit a vote center on Election Day. <br />Remember to bring an active and in&#8211;state ID to your local vote center. Examples in King County (WA) include: <br />• Driver’s license <br />• State ID card <br />• Student ID card <br />• Tribal ID card <br />• Employer ID card <br />Outside King County, check for accepted IDs here at voteriders.org and visit the vote center assigned for your address. <br />In some states you may need to request a provisional ballot that will be counted once the election office verifies that you have only submitted one ballot. <br />Other scenarios: <br />I made a mistake on my ballot. <br />Work with your local elections office to correct any errors. <br />I don’t have an ID. <br />Request a provisional ballot and you can still vote. Work with your elections office after Election Day to validate your ballot and it will be counted.</string>
    <string name="find_vote_center">Find Vote Center</string>
    <string name="_09">09</string>
    <string name="remind_your_community_to_vote">Remind Your Community to Vote</string>
    <string name="remind_your_comunity_to_vote_description">Remember to remind your family, friends, neighbors and coworkers to register to vote by the registration deadline, and vote in&#8211;person or drop off your ballot by Election Day at 8 pm.</string>
    <string name="_10">10</string>
    <string name="wait_for_election_results_description">Now it’s time to see who won the popular vote. Watch your local TV stations and most news stations to view the results as they come in from your state and others across the United States. <br />Regardless of the results, this is the time for you to celebrate your voice being heard and to build a plan to get further involved with civic engagement if preferred. Here are just a few ideas: <br />• Run for office (local, county, statewide, or federal) <br />• Volunteer/Work on a candidate’s campaign <br />• Volunteer/Work for a campaign/lobbying or voter registration organization <br />• Volunteer/Work for a group that covers the elections <br />• Organize your own voter drive <br />• Get others in your community involved in civic engagement</string>
    <string name="back">back</string>
    <string name="appointment_hours">Appointment Hours</string>
    <string name="appointment_hours_description">Tuesday-Wednesday: 11:30 am to 7:00 p.m.<br /> Friday - 11:30 a.m. to 7:00 p.m.<br /> Saturday - 10:00 a.m. to 4:30 p.m.</string>
    <string name="appointment_description">Gay City: Seattle’s LGBTQ Center offers confidential and anonymous HIV testing and STI screening. Testing includes Rapid HIV Testing (finger poke), HIV antibody testing, and screening for syphilis, chlamydia, gonorrhea, and Hep C.</string>
    <string name="make_an_appointment">Make an Appointment</string>
    <string name="image_for_appointment_tab">Image for appointment tab</string>
    <string name="instagram">Instagram</string>
    <string name="connect_with_us">Connect with Us</string>
    <string name="social_media">Social Media</string>
    <string name="twitter">Twitter</string>
    <string name="youtube">YouTube</string>
    <string name="contact_us">Contact Us</string>
    <string name="gaycity_phone">206&#8211;860&#8211;6969</string>
    <string name="resource_helpline">Resource Helpline</string>
    <string name="resource_helpline_number">206&#8211;323&#8211;LGBT</string>
    <string name="_24_hour_crisis_line">24&#8211;Hour Crisis Line</string>
    <string name="_24_hour_crisi_number">866&#8211;427&#8211;4747</string>
    <string name="email_lowecase">Email</string>
    <string name="gaycity_email">info@gaycity.org</string>
    <string name="facebook">Facebook</string>
    <string name="phone_lowercase">Phone</string>
    <string name="ways_to_give">Ways to Give</string>
    <string name="ways_to_give_description">Thank you for making a difference! Your vital support of Gay City ensures that people have a safe and welcoming space to gather and find meaningful connections. <br />Whether it’s our vibrant arts programming, our resource center connecting people to vital services, the affirming and sensitive care of our wellness center team, or a cozy chair in our LGBTQ library, there’s something for everyone, and all of this happens because of donors like you. <br />Thank you for supporting our mission to promote self&#8211;determination, liberation, and joy in our communities. Because of you, Gay City can continue to be a place for LGBTQ communities to thrive.</string>
    <string name="donate_now">Donate Now</string>
    <string name="health_insurance">Health Insurance</string>
    <string name="health_insurance_description">Get Enrolled in health insurance plan (including Apple Health) with the assistance of a multilingual LGBTQ health navigator today. We will help you enroll in the plan that works bets for you.<br />Enrollment services are available online and by phone</string>
    <string name="enroll_today">Enroll Today</string>
    <string name="image_in_health_insurance_tab">Image in health insurance tab</string>
    <string name="up_arrow_description">up arrow to go to top of page</string>
    <string name="welcome_to_the_gay_city_app">Welcome to The Gay City App</string>
    <string name="our_mission_uppercase">OUR MISSION</string>
    <string name="our_mission_homepage_description">Gay City: Seattle\'s LGBTQ Center cultivates ACCESS and conections to promote self&#8211;determination, liberation and joy in our communities</string>
    <string name="events">EVENTS</string>
    <string name="orca_lift">ORCA LIFT</string>
    <string name="orca_lift_description">Get more out of your public transportation system today with ORCA LIFT, a reduced&#8211;fare transit program. Whether traveling to work, school, or the mall, you can save money starting today.<br />King County Navigators are available by phone 8 a.m. to 6 p.m. and through online registration.<br />Load an e&#8211;purse value on your card to pay for trips one at a time, or load a discounted monthly pass that lets you take unlimited trips for an entire month.</string>
    <string name="where_do_orca_cards_work">Where do ORCA LIFT cards work?</string>
    <string name="where_orca_cards_work">• Metro Transit buses<br />• Community Transit buses<br />• Everett Transit buses<br />• Kitsap Transit buses<br />• Sound Transit Regional Express buses<br />• Sound Transit Link light rail<br />• Sounder Trains<br />• King County Water Taxi<br />• Seattle Streetcar</string>
    <string name="college_student_online_registration">College Student Online Registration</string>
    <string name="non_student_online_registration">Non&#8211;Student Online Registration</string>
    <string name="orca_phone">Phone Registration:<br /> Call 1&#8211;800&#8211;756&#8211;5437 to register over the phone<br />Questions?<br /> Contact us at info@gaycity.org or 206&#8211;860&#8211;6969</string>
    <string name="outreach">Outreach</string>
    <string name="outreach_description">Invite your local LGBTQ center to your community event. Gay City always seeks opportunities to connect LGBTQ+ communities to resources, provide HIV/STI testing and educate allies about the organization.<br />The Outreach/tabling team members require at least two&#8211;weeks notice prior to the event(s).<br />To request members from our outreach team to table at your upcoming event, please click the button below to complete the request form. After submitting the form, we will reach out to you within 10 business days with next steps.</string>
    <string name="image_in_outreach_tab">image in outreach tab</string>
    <string name="is_prep_right_for_me">Is PrEP Right For Me?</string>
    <string name="PrEP_description">One pill a day is all it takes to reduce your risk of HIV.<br />Our Gay City PrEP team can help you determine whether Pre&#8211;Exposure Prophylaxis (PrEP) is right for you.<br />We can help you find access to PrEP (whether insured or uninsured) and assistance to pay for the medication, or provide you with tips on how to talk about PrEP with your doctor.<br />The Gay city PrEP team is here to help and answer all questions about PrEP</string>
    <string name="contact_the_prep_team">Contact the PrEP Team</string>
    <string name="emergency_prep">EMERGENCY PrEP</string>
    <string name="emergency_PrEP_description">If you an urgent need or request about PrEP, contact us at PrEP@gaycity.org and include \"Urgent\" in the subject line.</string>
    <string name="accessing_pep">Accessing PEP</string>
    <string name="accessing_PEP_description">If you are concerned that you have been exposed to HIV in the last 72 hours, please visit any medical emergency room and request PEP (Post Exposure Prophylaxis).</string>
    <string name="queer_community_conversations">Queer Community Conversations</string>
    <string name="QCC_description">Queer and Trans folks are among the most impacted by COVID&#8211;19. We’re more likely to work in jobs that require us to be visible in the community and physically be present in the workplace. <br />Learn about concerns affecting our community in Washington State during COVID&#8211;19, share queer&#8211;affirming resources, and create a space for LGBTQ voices to be heard.</string>
    <string name="qcc_events">QCC Events</string>
    <string name="there_are_currently_no_events">There are currently no events</string>
    <string name="error_could_not_pull_resources_from_database">Error: could not pull Resources from database</string>
    <string name="resource_database">Resource Database</string>
    <string name="technical_assistance">Technical Assistance</string>
    <string name="image_in_technical_assistance_tab">image in technical assistance tab</string>
    <string name="technical_assistance_description">Gay City provides leading trainers and educators who will provide in&#8211;depth training and technical guidance based on your needs.<br />From making your company culture inclusive of LGBTQ communities to building motivational interviewing skills, Gay City can fulfill your needs.<br />Trainers require at least two&#8211;weeks notice prior to the training and technical assistance.<br />To request a training, please click the button below to complete the form. After submitting the form, we will reach out to you within 10 business days with next steps.</string>
    <string name="submit_request">Submit Request</string>
    <string name="view_testing_results">View Testing Results</string>
    <string name="testing_results_description">Gay City clients can view, download, and print their HIV/STI testing results online for free. No more waiting for the results phone line to open.<br />Testers will invite clients to use the Patient Portal during their appointment. if clients agree, they can check results here</string>
    <string name="check_results">Check Results</string>
    <string name="testing_results_astrisk">*All results will be available to clients within two weeks. Please note that our testing team will contact clients with positive results before they are posted</string>
    <string name="volunteer">Volunteer</string>
    <string name="volunteer_covid">In&#8211;person volunteering postponed during current phase of COVID&#8211;19 outbreak.</string>
    <string name="volunteer_description">At Gay City, your volunteer experience has real, tangible results. Whether helping to produce Gay City special events or assisting in one of our office spaces, you’ll see the impact live and in&#8211;person. Use your personal experiences to create programs and determine how they will help support the community. <br />You control your shift time, commitment and depth of involvement. <br />So jump on in! Experience the fun, challenge, and excitement of volunteering at Gay City.</string>
    <string name="image_in_volunteer_tab">image in volunteer tab</string>
    <string name="vote_for_visibility">Vote for Visibility</string>
    <string name="vote_for_visibility_description">For the past 14 years, LGBTQ people have proportionately voted at lower rates than non&#8211;LGBTQ+ voters. It’s our elected officials who will approve education, employment, and health care bills that affect our communities. They will determine how to use the census data to influence the resources we need in our community. <br />This year, join us at the polls. Stand with your community and fight for an affirming, queer&#8211;inclusive world. <br />Let’s vote and increase LGBTQ+ visibility at the polls.</string>
    <string name="_10_ways_to_prep_for_an_election">10 Ways to Prep for an Election</string>
    <string name="_10_ways_to_prepare_description">We’re consistently being hit with misinformation and voter suppression tricks. Time to counter it with our own tactic – knowledge – with 10 ways to prep before visiting the polls or requesting your ballot.</string>
    <string name="request_absentee_ballot">Request Absentee Ballot</string>
    <string name="change_address">Change Address</string>
    <string name="accessible_voting">Accessible Voting</string>
    <string name="image_in_vote_for_visibility_tab">image in vote for visibility tab</string>
    <string name="resource_database_resource_background">resource database resource background</string>
    <string name="location_for_potential_image">location for potential image</string>
</resources>